rechargencoupons.com 2016-10-04

# Recharge BOX: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Recharge Box collects, uses, maintains and discloses information. collected from users of the. www.rechargencoupons.com website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Recharge Box.

Information Collection And Use:  
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is  
not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number (“Personal Information”).

Web browser cookies:  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Note: Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

How we protect your information:  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and  
security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Contact Us:  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [gulsingh220@gmail.com](mailto:gulsingh220@gmail.com)
